ispwp.com 2010-02-04

# Privacy Policy | Wedding Photography | ISPWP | Best Wedding Photographer Directory

**Privacy Policy Statement**  
This is the web site of the International Society of Professional Wedding Photographers, hereafter knows as “ISPWP.” The ISPWP respects your privacy.

Our postal address is  
1464 SE 37th Ave.  
Hillsboro, OR,  USA, 97123  
We can be reached via e-mail at admin@ispwp.com

**General Policy**  
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of International Society of Professional Wedding Photographers (ISPWP).

**Information Collected**  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the e-mail address or any personal information.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our blog and the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

**Information Disclosed**  
The information we collect is disclosed when legally required to do so at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

**Cookies**  
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows websites to recognize you each time you visit the site for a variety of reasons (site customization, etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and the ISPWP does not use or set any cookies to collect personal information.

**Email**  
E-mail addresses, postal addresses, and phone numbers will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of International Society of Professional Wedding Photographers (ISPWP). If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

**Postal Address**  
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

**Telephone Numbers**  
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

**Ad Servers**  
With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with any ad server companies.

**Changes to Policy**  
If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

**Request for Information**  
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address.

**Secure Servers**  
When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we process all financial transactions over a secure server.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above email address.
